<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Shawn Lepp Group</title>
    <description>Shawn Lepp, a top Real Estate Agent in Durham, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 14:42:31 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 14:42:31 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Best Tips and Tricks for Following Up With Leads</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/dB1sSin6J08?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;&lt;em&gt;Need some tips and tricks for following up with leads and landing those appointments? Today I&amp;rsquo;ll give you my advice.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing I always tell agents looking for advice about following up with leads is to make sure that you call them back immediately. Don’t wait hours or even 10 minutes to return the call; people expect timely responses, so call back as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re at an appointment when you receive a call from a potential lead, send them a quick email or text to let them know that you’re currently at an appointment and that you’ll call them back shortly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s vital that you actually follow through with the promise to call them back&lt;/strong&gt;. People don’t always answer their phones, so be sure to send a text to let them know who was calling, why you called, and that you’ll follow up with them in a few hours. Many times, it’ll take six or seven attempts before the prospect will call you back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, &lt;strong&gt;don’t leave your lead on your phone&lt;/strong&gt;. Put that person’s contact information into your database. Here at the Shawn Lepp Group, we have a 33-touch and an 8x8 system in place to automatically follow up with leads via email, text messages, and if we have their physical address, through the mail. We like to reach out to them at least six or seven times in the first two weeks to make sure we’re branding ourselves so they know who we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Don’t wait hours or even 10 minutes to return the call; people expect timely responses, so call back as soon as possible.%20localhost:4000/my-best-tips-and-tricks-for-following-up-with-leads.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Don’t wait hours or even 10 minutes to return the call; people expect timely responses, so call back as soon as possible.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on the question that they’ve asked us, there are some different setups that we will follow. If it’s a listing lead and they’re asking for a home evaluation, &lt;strong&gt;we will send some materials to their home address and email them some videos&lt;/strong&gt; about our team to let them know what kind of services we offer. &lt;strong&gt;If it’s a buyer lead, we’ll ask them if they’ve seen any houses they’re interested in yet&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever we do, it’s critically important to make contact more than once. They say &lt;strong&gt;the best conversion time is between the sixth and tenth time you contact someone&lt;/strong&gt;, while most agents, if they actually call back, will stop after the first call.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ultimately, the key is to make sure you put these leads into your database and that you continue to follow up with their inquiries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like more information regarding the best tips, tricks, and systems we use to land those appointments, feel free to reach out to me. I’d love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/my-best-tips-and-tricks-for-following-up-with-leads.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/my-best-tips-and-tricks-for-following-up-with-leads.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
